#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/johannesreck (LinkedIn)

www.getyourguide.com (Other) blog.getyourguide.com (Other) www.getyourguide.com/apps/ (Other)

### Top Skills

Venture Capital
Management Consulting
Start-ups

### Languages

German

English

French

# Johannes Reck

Co-Founder & CEO at GetYourGuide

Berlin Metropolitan Area

## Summary

Johannes graduated as Master of Science from the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology in January 2009 with highest honors. While still in university, he co-founded GetYourGuide with the vision to help travelers to find and book incredible travel experiences.

GetYourGuide has since become one of the most successful companies in the history of online travel and is providing millions of travelers with incredible experiences, wherever they go.

We're hiring! Please visit our job's page for the latest openings! http://www.getyourguide.com/jobs.php

Check out our great mobile apps! http://www.getyourguide.com/apps/

## Experience

GetYourGuide Co-Founder and CEO June 2009 - Present (12 years 11 months)

We are changing the way how people travel.

The Boston Consulting Group Visiting Associate February 2009 - May 2009 (4 months)

Management Consulting for major corporations in Pharma & Finance

### Education

Eidgenössische Technische Hochschule Zürich MSc, Biochemistry · (2007 - 2009)

ETH Zürich

BSc, Biochemistry · (2004 - 2007)